CHANDLER! CHANDLER!
( grunting )
CHANDLER, I SAW WHAT
YOU WERE DOING
THROUGH THE WINDOW!
I SAW WHAT YOU WERE DOING
TO MY SISTER!
NOW, GET OUT HERE!
WELL, LISTEN,
WE HAD A GOOD RUN.
YOU KNOW, WHAT WAS IT--
FOUR, FIVE MONTHS?
I MEAN, THAT'S MORE
THAN MOST PEOPLE HAVE
IN A LIFETIME.
SO, GOOD-BYE, TAKE CARE,
BYE-BYE, DEAR.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, I'M GOING
ON THE LAM.
COME ON, CHANDLER,
COME ON.
I CAN HANDLE ROSS.
HOLD ON.
HEY, ROSS.
WHAT'S UP, BRO?
WHAT...
THE HELL...
ARE YOU DOING?!
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
WELL, I THINK...
I THINK ROSS KNOWS
ABOUT ME AND MONICA?
DUDE, HE'S RIGHT THERE...
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
MY BEST FRIEND.
THIS IS MY SISTER!
MY BEST FRIEND AND MY SISTER.
I CANNOT BELIEVE THIS!
LOOK, WE'RE NOT JUST
MESSING AROUND.
I LOVE HER, OKAY?
I'M IN LOVE WITH HER.
I'M SO SORRY THAT YOU
HAD TO FIND OUT THIS WAY.
I'M SORRY, BUT IT-IT'S TRUE.
I-I LOVE HIM, TOO.
MY BEST FRIEND
AND MY SISTER!
I'M SO HAPPY!
I CANNOT BELIEVE THIS!
OH, I'M SORRY,
YOU GUYS WANT
TO PROBABLY GET SOME
HUGS IN, TOO, HUH?
BIG NEWS!
OH, NO, THAT'S OKAY.
WE'VE ACTUALLY KNOWN
FOR A WHILE.
WHAT-WHAT?
YOU GUYS KNEW?
YOU ALL KNEW
AND YOU DIDN'T TELL ME?!
WELL, ROSS, WE WERE
WORRIED ABOUT YOU, OKAY?
WE DIDN'T KNOW HOW
YOU WERE GOING TO REACT.
MMM.
YOU WERE WORRIED ABOUT ME?
YOU DIDN'T KNOW HOW
I WAS GOING TO REACT?
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
WHEW!
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE ALL,
UH, CLEAR OUT OF HERE
AND LET THESE TWO LOVEBIRDS
GET BACK DOWN TO BUSINESS?
HEY, HEY, HEY,
I-I'M JUST TALKING HERE.
HE'S THE ONE
DOING YOUR SISTER.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HEY, YOU KNOW
WHAT I JUST REALIZED?
IF YOU GUYS EVER HAVE KIDS...
WHOA, WHOA,
WE'RE HAVING KIDS?
I CALL GODFATHER.
YOU CAN'T JUST CALL
GODFATHER.
DON'T YOU THINK HER BROTHER
SHOULD BE GODFATHER?
SURE, IF YOU CARED ENOUGH
TO CALL IT FIRST.
YOU GUYS...
I THINK YOU'RE A FEW
STEPS AHEAD OF US.
YEAH. BIG ZERO-GRAVITY
MOON STEPS.
OH, I JUST THOUGHT
OF THE GREATEST WEDDING GIFT
TO GET YOU.
OOH, I'LL GO IN
ON THAT WITH YOU.
I COULDN'T THINK
OF ANYTHING.
OH. HI, KATIE.
HEY, EVERYONE,
THIS IS KATIE.
HI.
Joey:
SO, ARE YOU
READY TO GO?
I JUST GOT TO RUN
TO THE BATHROOM.
BACK THERE.
HEY, WHERE WE GOING
TO LUNCH?
I WAS THINKING
MAYBE CHINESE FOOD.
OH, I LOVE CHINESE!
HOW'D YOU KNOW
I LOVE CHINESE?!
SHE IS SO CUTE.
YOU COULD FIT HER
RIGHT IN YOUR LITTLE POCKET.
I DON'T KNOW...
I MEAN, I LIKE HER A LOT,
AND SHE'S REALLY NICE, BUT...
BUT WHAT?
SHE KEEPS PUNCHING ME.
( chuckling )
IN THAT CUTE, LITTLE
SWEET WAY SHE JUST DID?
HEY, IT'S A LOT HARDER
THAN IT LOOKS, OKAY?
SHE-SHE... SHE'S HURTING ME.
OH, SEE, I KNOW
WHAT YOU NEED.
YOU NEED A BODYGUARD.
ROSS, WHAT IS BEN DOING
AFTER PRESCHOOL?
OKAY, LISTEN--
JOEY IS HAVING A PROBLEM...
WITH A LITTLE GIRL
WHO'S BEATING HIM UP.
AW... JOEY, COME HERE.
LOOK-- HONEY, I KNOW
THIS MUST BE
REALLY, REALLY DIFFICULT
FOR YOU...
OH, I'M SORRY.
AM I HURTING YOU?
( blowing )
( knocking )
HEY!
HEY! I BROUGHT YOU
SOME HOUSEWARMING GIFTS.
OH...
YEAH-- SALT, SO YOUR LIFE
ALWAYS HAS FLAVOR...
OH.
BREAD, SO YOU NEVER
GO HUNGRY...
OH...
AND A SCENTED CANDLE
FOR THE BATHROOM
BECAUSE, WELL, YOU KNOW.
WELL, THANKS, THANKS,
AND... THANKS, I GUESS.
YEAH!
HI.
WELCOME TO THE BUILDING.
I'M STEVE SERRA, PRESIDENT
OF THE TENANTS COMMITTEE.
OH, HI. ROSS GELLER.
AND THIS IS MY FRIEND,
PHOEBE.
HI, PHOEBE.
MR. PRESIDENT.
I, UH, CAME TO TALK
TO YOU ABOUT HOWARD.
HOWARD?
YEAH. HE'S THE HANDYMAN.
HE'S RETIRING NEXT WEEK,
AND EVERYONE WHO LIVES HERE
IS KICKING IN
A HUNDRED BUCKS
AS A "THANK YOU FOR
ALL OF THE HARD WORK"
TYPE OF THING.
OH, THAT'S NICE.
YEAH. YOU WANT TO GIVE
ME A CHECK OR...?
( chuckling ):
OH! UH...
LOOK, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO GIVE IT
TO ME RIGHT NOW.
YOU CAN SLIP IT
UNDER MY DOOR...
NO, NO, IT'S NOT THAT.
IT'S JUST, I...
I-I JUST MOVED IN.
WELL, THE GUY'S WORKED
HERE FOR 25 YEARS.
YES, BUT I'VE LIVED HERE
FOR 25 MINUTES.
OH.
( Ross chuckles )
OKAY. I GET IT.
NO, WAIT. LOOK, LOOK...
I'M SORRY, IT'S JUST I'VE
NEVER EVEN MET... HOWARD.
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW HOWARD.
HOWARD'S THE HANDYMAN?
YES, BUT TO ME HE'S JUST...
MAN.
OKAY, FINE.
WHATEVER.
( coldly ):
WELCOME TO THE BUILDING.
( scoffing )
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT GUY?
YEAH. I REALLY LIKE
HIS GLASSES.
...SO THEN PRESIDENT
STEVE TOLD EVERYONE
I WAS A CHEAPSKATE
AND NOW THE WHOLE
BUILDING HATES ME.
YOU KNOW, A LITTLE KID
SPIT ON MY KNEE.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M GOING TO DO?
I'M GOING TO THROW
A PARTY--
THAT'S RIGHT,
FOR EVERYONE
IN THE BUILDING.
I'M GOING TO SIT
THEM ALL DOWN
AND EXPLAIN TO THEM THAT
I AM NOT A BAD GUY.
I AM NOT A CHEAP GUY.
I'M JUST A GUY
WHO-WHO STANDS UP
FOR WHAT HE BELIEVES
IN, A MAN...
( tapping finger ):
WITH PRINCIPLES.
SOUNDS LIKE A FUN PARTY.
LOOK, ROSS, IF YOU WANT
YOUR NEIGHBORS TO LIKE YOU
WHY DON'T YOU JUST PAY
THE HUNDRED BUCKS?
A PARTY'S GOING TO COST YOU
WAY MORE THAN THAT.
THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
IT'S MY PRINCIPLES.
WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT MY PRINCIPLES!
OKAY.
I THOUGHT IT WAS ABOUT
YOUR NEIGHBORS LIKING YOU.
OH, THEY'LL LIKE ME ONCE THEY
COME TO MY AWESOME PAR-TAY.
OKAY, I GOT TO RUN.
I GOT TO GO GET SOME NAME TAGS.
( door closes )
AND THAT CRAZY PARTY ANIMAL
WILL BE YOUR BROTHER-IN-LAW.
OH, YEAH. VERY, VERY FUNNY.
BUT DON'T SAY THINGS LIKE THAT
IN FRONT OF MONICA.
I DON'T WANT YOU PUTTING
ANY IDEAS IN HER HEAD.
UM, CHANDLER,
YOU-YOU DO REALIZE
THAT THOSE IDEAS ARE PROBABLY
ALREADY IN MONICA'S HEAD?
WH-WHY?
WELL, BECAUSE SHE LOVES YOU
AND BECAUSE YOU LOVE HER.
YEAH? SO? WHAT'S THAT'S
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
HEY, CHANDLER, DON'T FREAK OUT.
I'M TELLING YOU SOMETHING
YOU ALREADY KNOW.
COME ON, SHE BROKE UP
WITH RICHARD
BECAUSE HE DIDN'T WANT
TO HAVE BABIES
AND SHE'S A WOMAN, AND SHE'S
ALMOST 30, AND, YOU KNOW...
IT'S MONICA.
I DON'T SEE IT THAT WAY, OKAY?
BECAUSE I SEE TWO MONICAS--
THE ONE THAT WAS MY FRIEND
WHO LIVES ACROSS THE HALL
AND WANTED TO HAVE
A LOT OF BABIES...
AND THEN THE NEW MONICA,
WHO I JUST STARTED TO DATE.
OKAY, NOW, WHO'S TO SAY
WHAT SHE WANTS?
I'M RIGHT. I'M RIGHT.
AM I RIGHT?
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT,
YOU ARE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
I MEAN, THAT MAKES
EVERYTHING DIFFERENT.
OKAY.
( opens pop top )
IT'S NOT DIFFERENT
AT ALL, IS IT?
NOT UNLESS "DIFFERENT" MEANS
"THE SAME."
YOU WERE SO FUNNY
WITH THAT WAITER.
YOU'RE SUCH A NUT!
WELL, YOU KNOW,
BREADSTICK FANGS
ARE ALWAYS FUNNY, SO...
NO, YOU MAKE THEM FUNNY.
YOU'RE THE FUNNY ONE!
THANKS.
UH, LOOK, KATIE, UH...
LISTEN, WE-WE NEED
TO TALK, OKAY?
UM, LOOK, I LIKE YOU--
I-I REALLY DO.
I LIKE YOU A LOT, OKAY?
BUT SOMETIMES WHEN YOU
PLAYFULLY PUNCH ME LIKE THAT
IT-IT FEELS LIKE
SOMEONE'S HITTING ME
WITH A VERY TINY,
BUT A VERY REAL BAT.
OH... LIKE I COULD HURT YOU.
ARE YOU MAKING FUN
OF MY SIZE?
NO.
DON'T MAKE FUN OF ME
BECAUSE OF MY SIZE!
YEAH, OKAY.
OH...
HMM...
ISN'T THIS GREAT?
MMM.
COULDN'T YOU JUST STAY
LIKE THIS FOREVER?
CHANDLER?
COULDN'T YOU JUST
STAY HERE FOREVER?
YEAH, HERE, SOMEWHERE ELSE...
YOU KNOW, WHERE-WHEREVER.
( nervous chuckle )
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH. I'M COOL.
CASUAL.
WHAT-WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, JUST HANGING OUT,
YOU KNOW, HAVING FUN...
YOU KNOW, WITH THE GIRL
THAT I'M SEEING CASUALLY.
( scoffing ):
OH... MAN, I KNEW IT.
I KNEW YOU WERE GOING
TO DO THIS.
WHAT?
GET ALL FREAKED OUT
BECAUSE EVERYBODY WAS TALKING
AND JUST JOKING AROUND
ABOUT MARRIAGE AND STUFF.
WELL, YOU-YOU DO WANT
ALL THAT STUFF, RIGHT?
OH, AND YOU KNOW WHAT I WANT.
YES. YOU WANT BABIES.
YOU HAVE BABY FEVER.
I DO NOT HAVE BABY FEVER.
OH, PLEASE. YOU ARE OBSESSED
WITH BABIES AND MARRIAGE
AND EVERYTHING THAT'S
RELATED TO BABIES
AND-AND... MARRIAGE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I GOT A GOOD IDEA.
WHY DON'T WE TURN
THE HEAT DOWN
ON THIS
PRESSURE COOKER?!
HAVE YOU LOST YOUR MIND?
CHANDLER, THIS ISN'T ABOUT ME;
THIS IS ABOUT YOU
AND ALL YOUR WEIRD
RELATIONSHIP COMMITMENT CRAP.
NUH-UH. I KNOW YOU, OKAY?
I KNOW THE THOUGHTS
THAT YOU HAVE
IN THE HEAD--
IN YOUR HEAD.
WELL, YOU DON'T KNOW EVERYTHING.
DID YOU KNOW THAT I'M GOING OUT
WITH RACHEL TONIGHT
INSTEAD OF YOU, HMM?
AND DID YOU KNOW THAT THE ONLY
BABY AROUND HERE IS YOU?
AND DID YOU KNOW
THAT I CAN'T EVEN
LOOK AT YOU RIGHT NOW?
YEAH, WELL, I DID NOT KNOW THAT.
THIS IS GOING
TO BE OKAY, RIGHT?
I MEAN, SHE'S NOT
GOING TO LEAVE ME.
THIS IS FIXABLE.
SURE.
ABSOLUTELY.
BY ME.
OH, NO.
NO, NO, NO.
WELL, UNLESS YOU MAKE
SOME KIND OF BIG GESTURE.
Joey:
YEAH, BIG, THOUGH.
UH-OH! SHH! THE MISSUS.
GUNTHER, CAN I
GET A COFFEE?
TO GO?
LOOK, MONICA...
I'M STILL NOT DONE
NOT WANTING TO TALK TO YOU.
JUST TELL ME
WHAT I NEED TO DO
TO MAKE THINGS RIGHT.
WHAT?
THAT'S WHAT WE DO.
I MESS UP, AND THEN YOU
TELL ME HOW TO FIX IT
AND THEN I DO, AND THEN YOU
THINK I'M ALL CUTE AGAIN.
I'M REALLY TIRED OF BEING
YOUR RELATIONSHIP TUTOR.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO FIGURE THIS ONE OUT
FOR YOURSELF, ALL RIGHT?
IF YOU'RE TOO AFRAID
TO BE IN A REAL RELATIONSHIP
THEN DON'T
BE IN ONE.
( chanting ):
HOWARD! HOWARD!
PHOEBE?
HOWARD!
HOWARD! YAY!
OH, HI, ROSS!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, I THOUGHT
THIS WAS YOUR PARTY
AND IT TURNS OUT,
IT'S A PARTY FOR HOWARD.
HE'S THE SWEETEST LITTLE MAN.
SEE YA, PHOEBE.
OH, AND, HEY, THANKS
FOR CHIPPING IN.
OH, SURE.
YOU CHIPPED IN?
YEAH, UH-HUH. $100.
PHOEBE, I-I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU GAVE HIM MONEY.
I THOUGHT YOU AGREED
IT WAS TRULY UNREASONABLE
THAT THEY ASKED ME
FOR THAT MONEY.
YEAH, BUT THEY
DIDN'T ASK ME, YOU KNOW
AND THIS WAY I'M JUST
THE EXOTIC, GENEROUS STRANGER
AND THAT'S ALWAYS FUN TO BE.
YEAH, BUT YOU'RE
MAKING ME LOOK BAD.
NO, I'M NOT. NO.
IF ANYTHING, I'M MAKING
YOU LOOK BETTER.
THEY'LL SEE YOU TALKING
TO ME, AND THAT'S, YOU KNOW.
I'M A HIT.
HEY, PHEEBS.
HEY.
OH, HEY, ROSS.
UM, SAY, I WAS THINKING
MAYBE YOU TWO COULD
SWITCH APARTMENTS
'CAUSE PHOEBE'S MORE
OUR KIND OF PEOPLE.
SOMETHING TO THINK ABOUT.
YEAH, OKAY, MY BAD.
HEY.
HI.
WOW, YOU LOOK...
YOU LOOK BIG.
THANKS. I'VE BEEN WORKING OUT.
HEY, LISTEN, IS IT OBVIOUS
I'M WEARING SIX SWEATERS?
UH, YEAH. BUT IT'S
NOT OBVIOUS WHY.
WELL, LOOK, I'M BREAKING UP
WITH KATIE.
SO I HAD TO PUT ON
SOME EXTRA PADDING.
I MEAN, IF SHE HITS ME
WHEN SHE'S HAPPY
CAN YOU IMAGINE HOW HARD
SHE'S GOING TO HIT ME
WHEN I TELL HER
I'M TAKING AWAY THE JOEY LOVE?
HEY.
HOW ARE YOU?
HEY, CUTE JACKET.
OH, THANKS.
THAT'S SO SWEET.
WHOA.
OW!
( laughing )
OH, "OW." DID JOEY
TELL YOU TO SAY THAT?
YOU GUYS
ARE TOO MUCH.
WHOA.
YOU KNOW WHAT, KATIE?
I GOT TO TELL YOU.
I-I-I THINK YOU'RE
THE ONE THAT IS TOO MUCH.
OH, JOEY HAS
THE NICEST FRIENDS.
OH, AND THE NICEST GIRLFRIEND.
OH...
YOU'RE SO SWEET.
WELL, YOU'RE SO SWEET.
OW!
JOEY... SHE
JUST KICKED ME.
HUH.
WELL?
AREN'T YOU GOING
TO DO SOMETHING?
UH...
YOU'D BETTER DO SOMETHING
OR I'M GOING TO WALK
OUT THAT DOOR RIGHT NOW.
WELL?
ARE YOU GONNA?
NAH.
( laughing )
PHOEBE?
THAT'S WHAT
I WAS SAYING.
PHOEBE, PHOEBE...
OOH.
LOOK, THIS IS A DISASTER.
CAN'T I PLEASE
JUST GO?
NO, NO. I'M TALKING
YOU UP TO PEOPLE.
JUST GIVE IT
A LITTLE TIME, ALL RIGHT?
RELAX. GET SOMETHING TO EAT.
OKAY?
SO, UH, WHAT
DID YOU TELL
THEM ABOUT ME?
UM, OH, I WAS TELLING THEM
ABOUT YOU AND EMILY.
YOU KNOW, TRY
TO GET SOME SYMPATHY?
BUT SOMEHOW YOU CAME OFF
AS THE BAD GUY.
WHAT?
YEAH. I THINK
I TOLD IT WRONG.
YOU KNOW, WE SHOULD TALK
ABOUT THAT
'CAUSE I DON'T TOTALLY
UNDERSTAND
WHAT HAPPENED THERE.
OOH, THIS CAKE
IS REALLY GOOD.
SEE? THINGS
ARE LOOKING UP ALREADY.
OH, MY GOD, SOMEONE
CUT HOWARD'S CAKE.
WHO WOULD DO
A THING LIKE THAT?
3-B.
All:
OH, YEAH. AW, COME ON.
OKAY, YOU GOT YOUR FREE FOOD,
YOU RUINED EVERYONE'S FUN.
DON'T YOU THINK IT'S TIME
YOU WENT HOME?
All:
HEY, GO HOME.
GO BACK TO 3-B, 3-B.
OKAY, EVERYONE?
EVERYONE CALM DOWN.
I HAVE SOMETHING
THAT I WOULD LIKE TO SAY.
WHO HERE LIKES ROSS?
WELL, OF COURSE
YOU DON'T LIKE HIM.
HE DIDN'T GIVE YOU ANY MONEY.
HE RAISED HIS OWN HAND WHEN I
ASKED, "WHO HERE LIKES ROSS?"
AND HE'S WEARING TWO NAME TAGS.
I'LL BE HONEST WITH YOU GUYS.
WHEN I FIRST MET ROSS,
I DIDN'T LIKE HIM AT ALL.
BUT THEN,
ONCE I GOT TO KNOW HIM
I SAW THAT HE'S REALLY SWEET
AND CARING
AND VERY GENEROUS.
I MEAN, ALL I'M SAYING
IS DON'T JUDGE ROSS
BEFORE YOU GET TO KNOW HIM,
ALL RIGHT?
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, I LIKE
ALL YOU GUYS NOW
BUT WHEN I FIRST MET YOU,
YOU KNOW... CURT--
I THOUGHT, YOU KNOW
"ABRASIVE DRUNK."
UM, LOLA--
"MIND-NUMBINGLY STUPID."
YOU KNOW, AND...
OKAY, YOU GUYS
"GOLD-DIGGER,"
"CRADLE-ROBBING PERV."
SO I THINK YOU ALL KNOW
WHAT I MEAN.
OBVIOUSLY, I
DIDN'T THINK
THEY WERE GOING TO START
THROWING THINGS.
I JUST THOUGHT
IF I KEPT
INSULTING THEM
YOU WOULD JUMP IN
AND DEFEND EVERYONE
AND THEN YOU COULD
LOOK LIKE THE HERO.
OH, WOW, YEAH.
SEE, I DID NOT GET THAT.
WHERE'S MONICA?
I NEED TO TALK TO HER.
IT'S URGENT. IS SHE HERE?
I'M MONICA.
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
IT'S URGENT.
OKAY.
OKAY, I'VE BEEN DOING
A LOT OF THINKING
ABOUT US, YOU KNOW,
A LOT OF, UH, "US" THINKING
AND, UH... WELL, I GUESS
THERE'S ONLY ONE...
ONE WAY TO DO THIS.
NO, NO, NO.
WH-WHAT...? WHAT
ARE YOU DOING?
MONICA...
NO, NO, NO. DON'T...
DON'T DO IT.
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO.
WHAT A BAD IDEA.
OH, I CAN'T
NOT LOOK AT IT.
CHANDLER, WHY ARE
YOU DOING THIS?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I KNOW I'M NOT
AFRAID TO DO THIS.
CHANDLER...
I'M DOING THIS
BECAUSE I'M SORRY?
D-DO YOU, UM,
YOU REALLY THINK
THE BEST REASON
TO GET MARRIED
IS BECAUSE YOU'RE SORRY?
WELL, NO. THE BEST REASON
TO GET MARRIED
IS PREGNANCY.
BUT "SORRY"
IS PRETTY MUCH FOURTH
YOU KNOW,
BEHIND "BEING READY"
AND "ACTUALLY WANTING
TO GET MARRIED."
WILL YOU BE MY WIFE?
CHANDLER, UM, I WANT YOU
TO TAKE JUST A MINUTE
AND I WANT YOU
TO THINK ABOUT
HOW RIDICULOUS
THIS SOUNDS.
YEAH, I'M KIND OF WISHING
EVERYONE WASN'T HERE RIGHT NOW.
OH, HONEY,
DO YOU KNOW
THAT NONE OF THAT
STUFF CAME FROM ME?
I MEAN, I NEVER
SAID THAT I WANTED
TO HAVE BABIES AND
GET MARRIED RIGHT NOW.
YEAH, I KNOW, BUT I WAS
REALLY CONFUSED
AND THEN I TALKED
TO THESE GUYS
WHO, TWO-DIVORCES
AND JOEY?
HEY.
SHE'S RIGHT, YOU KNOW.
YEAH, BUT STILL,
CHEAP SHOT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU WHEN I WHEN I SAID
THAT I WANT YOU TO DEAL
WITH THIS RELATIONSHIP
STUFF ALL ON YOUR OWN?
WELL, YOU'RE NOT
READY FOR THAT.
I DIDN'T THINK I WAS.
COME HERE.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE DONE
IF I HAD SAID YES?
WELL, I WOULD HAVE BEEN HAPPY
BECAUSE I WOULD HAVE BEEN ABLE
TO SPEND THE REST OF MY LIFE
WITH THE WOMAN THAT I LOVE.
OR YOU WOULD HAVE SEEN
A CHANDLER-SHAPED HOLE
IN THAT DOOR.
WOULD YOU PASS ME
THAT KNIFE?
NO, I WILL NOT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
BE MEAN ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE RIGHT. I'M SORRY.
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
I WAS GOING TO ASK YOU
TO MARRY ME
'CAUSE I FORGOT TO SAY HELLO
TO YOU LAST WEEK.
OH, NO, WAIT,
PHEEBS, I THINK
WITH SOMETHING LIKE THAT,
YOU JUST ASK THEM
TO MOVE IN WITH YOU,
BUT I'M NOT SURE.
CHANDLER?
OKAY, HOW LONG
IS THIS GOING TO GO ON?
WELL, I THINK
THE LENGTH OF TEASING
IS DIRECTLY RELATED
TO HOW INSANE YOU WERE
SO A LONG TIME.
THIS IS FUN.
HEY, RACH, REMEMBER THAT WHOLE
"WE WERE ON A BREAK" THING?
WELL, I'M SORRY.
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
( only Ross laughs )
( laughter trails off )
All:
THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]